http://www.intelseek.com/terms.asp

Home   What's New?   Submit Your Site!   Last 12 Sites Submitted   Advertise with Us   Classified Ads   16 More!
See God in every person, place, and thing, and all will be well in your world. - Louise Hay
Search I.S.
Search On:
All Words
Any Words
General
MGA Web Productions and, its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively
"MGAWEB") provide you with access to this Web site
and the services available on this Web site, or other Web sites as indicated below, (collectively, the "Search Services," which may or may not be located on third party web sites and/or applications that third parties control). Access to and use of the Search Services is governed by these Terms of Use (the "Agreement"). By accessing or using the Search Services, you indicate your assent to be bound by the Agreement, and your acknowledgment of and agreement to its terms.
Search Services
Our Search Services enable you to search the World Wide Web for anything that interests you, whether, for example, "automotive", "business" or "home improvement." We may provide you with search listings of advertisers of
MGAWEB
(as well as search listings provided to
us
by a third party to supplement the advertiser listings) that help you find what you are
seeking.
MGAWEB
has many partner websites ("Affiliates") which display results of
our
searches. Advertiser links may appear and be accessible on partner websites. In such situations, and unless specifically informed otherwise, all advertiser links displayed in other mediums will include the full title, description and link provided to
us.
MGAWEB
reserves the right to remove any advertiser or website link at any time and for any reason. In the event that
we
remove an advertiser, all unspent funds will be returned to the advertiser. Reasons for removal may include, but are not limited to, sites promoting illegal materials, potentially infringing materials including trademark or copyright infringements, or racial or hate motivated sites.
Disclaimer of Warranties
THE SEARCH SERVICES ARE PROVIDED "AS IS," WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.
MGAWEB
DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING ANY WARRANTIES OF TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
MGAWEB's Potential Liability for the Services is Limited
NEITHER
MGAWEB
NOR ANY OF ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, AGENTS, SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, EMPLOYEES, SUCCESSORS, ASSIGNS, CONTENT PROVIDERS OR SERVICE PROVIDERS WILL BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF USE OF THE SERVICES, OR INABILITY TO GAIN ACCESS TO OR USE THE SERVICES.
MGAWEB
WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY MATERIAL OF WEB SITES IT LINKS TO AS PART OF THE SERVICES OR FOR INFORMATION CONTAINED IN OR PART OF THE SERVICES INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO SEARCH RESULTS. BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH STATES, THE RESPECTIVE LIABILITY OF
MGAWEB, ITS EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUCCESSORS, ASSIGNS, AFFILIATES, AND CONTENT OR SERVICE PROVIDERS IS LIMITED TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY SUCH STATE LAW.
Copyright and Trademark
You may not copy, reproduce or use in any other way the logo or web site without express written consent from
MGAWEB. Violators will be prosecuted to the full extent of the law. Please report copyright and/or trademark infringements to the following email address:
MGAWEB
E-Mail: info@MGAWEB.com
Objectionable Material and Family Filtering
MGAWEB
encourages you to use discretion when browsing the Internet or using the Services. The Services may contain information that you find objectionable, harmful, deceptive or otherwise inappropriate, especially for children. If this is a concern for you,
MGAWEB
encourages you to use an adult filtering service to ensure you do not receive offensive material. If you come across any site that you believe contains child pornography or other illegal material, please contact
info@MGAWEB.com and the appropriate authorities will be contacted.
Privacy and Data Collection
MGAWEB
does not collect personally identifying information from users of the Services unless users have explicitly given such information to
MGAWEB
(for example, when becoming an advertiser or when sending us an e-mail with a question or as part of a contest).
MGAWEB's information practices are further described in its privacy policy.
MGAWEB's privacy policy is part of this Agreement, and you agree that use of data as described in the privacy policy is not an actionable breach of your privacy or publicity rights. If you have entered into another agreement with
MGAWEB
(such as an Affiliate Agreement or an Advertiser Agreement), then you may be subject to additional or different provisions regarding privacy and data collection. If you would like more information, please read our privacy policy. You should consider any communication that you transmit to
MGAWEB
(such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that
MGAWEB
will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.
Access to Our Services
MGAWEB
reserves the right to modify any information, features and functions of the Services without prior notice.
MGAWEB
may deny you access to all or part of the Services without prior notice if you engage in any conduct or activities that
MGAWEB
determines, in its sole discretion, violate this Agreement, the rights of
MGAWEB
or any third party, or is otherwise inappropriate.
Choice of Law, Waiver, and Claims
This Agreement shall be governed by the laws of the State of Georgia without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
MGAWEB's failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the Agreement will not be deemed to be a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of this Agreement is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties' intentions as reflected in the provision, and the other provisions of this Agreement remain in full force and effect. You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to use of the Services must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred.
Notice
You may direct any questions concerning this Agreement to:
MGAWEB
info@MGAWEB.com
Amendment
MGAWEB
may amend this Agreement at any time by posting the amended terms on its Web site. This Agreement may not be otherwise amended except in a written document signed by you and
MGAWEB.  This agreement was last revised on Nov.
3, 2003.
Home   What's New?   Submit Your Site!   Last 12 Sites Submitted   Advertise with Us   Classified Ads   16 More!
Search Engine: © Copyright 2002 - 2020
MGA Web Productions All Rights Reserved.Contact Information: P.O. Box 6813, Thomasville, GA
31758  Ph: 229-227-6629 |
Email Us
Search Engine Terms of Use and Search Engine Privacy Policy
